人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：阿好  油炸电风扇  紫玉  板栗桑  麦结  Lemony
时间轴：烟幕迟迟   擦擦   Jessie
特效：灰灰是菇凉请假一个月勿念
校对&总监&压制：阿好今年要钓到帅如里叔萌如宅总的汉子
你被监视着
You are being watched.
政府有一套秘密系统
The government has a secret system--
一台每时每刻都在监控你的机器
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
联系系统管理员
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror
身份不明
但它却看到了一切
but it sees everything--
身份不明
牵涉普通人的暴力罪行
violent crimes involving ordinary people.
政府认为这些人无关紧要
The government considered these people irrelevant.
关键执行人
我们不
We don't.
失踪
关键执行人
受当局追捕  我们只能秘密活动
Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret.
状态：纽约警局任职
你永远找不到我们
You'll never find us.
但无论是受害人还是行凶者
But victim or perpetrator,
只要你的号码被列出来  我们就会找到你
if your number's up, we'll find you.
疑犯追踪
第二季 第十四集
被动手机麦克风
主体  哈里斯  查尔斯
会话分析
语言识别
哈里斯  查尔斯                                 卡扎维奇  桑亚
你看到怎么回事了吗
Did you see it happen?
没有  但她看到了  她什么都看到了
No, but she did. She saw everything.
那姑娘现在在哪里
Where's the girl now?
你能确保她的安全吗
Are you sure you can keep her safe?
塞尔维亚
当然
Of course.
纽 约
你知道第一个民用手机
Did you know that the first public cell phone call
是在纽约希尔顿酒店打出的吗  在1973年
was made from the New York Hilton? 1973.
还有传言说马提尼
There's also a rumor that the Martini
是在[旧金山]尼克伯克酒店发明的
was invented at the Knickerbocker,
不过有些旧金山人士
but there are some people in San Francisco
对此颇持异见
that would dispute that.
我感觉自己应该记笔记了
I feel like I should be taking notes.
你觉得我对酒店的痴迷很奇怪
You find my fascination with hotels to be peculiar,
是吧
don't you?
你能分享私事就很奇怪
You sharing anything personal is peculiar.
酒店是为数不多的
A hotel is one of the last few places
可以容人匿名其中的地方
where a person can retain relative anonymity.
所以在这里清理掉那些外交官
Makes it easier when disappearing foreign diplomats
比在他们的豪华公寓容易
from their penthouses.
走运的话  里瑟先生  我们可以阻止谋杀
With any luck, Mr. Reese, we can prevent a murder,
而非相反
rather than the alternative.
是啊
Yeah.
员工通道
米拉・杜布瑞卡
Mira Dobrica.
你确定威胁来自她的工作场所吗
You sure the threat to her is work-related?
杜布瑞卡女士单身  独居
Ms. Dobrica is single, lives alone,
没什么社交网络
doesn't do much social networking,
每周工作60小时
and she puts in a 60-hour work week.
要出事儿的话
Whatever's gonna happen,
应该就只会出在这里
it makes sense that it would happen here.
据说女佣能从一个人的房间
They say a maid can tell everything about you
看出此人的一切
from how you leave your room.
酒店房间里什么事都有
All sorts of things happen in hotel rooms.
米拉的工作有可能让她
Mira's job could have put her
在错误时间到了错误地方
at the wrong place at the wrong time.
她来美国前的生活如何
What about her life before coming to America?
有点神秘  她99年来的
Bit of a mystery. She came here in '99,
当时的电脑纪录可不像现在
when computer records weren't what they are today.
我以准雇主的身份打电话问移民局了
I put in a call to immigration services as a prospective employer.
是那个环球人寿保险的冉先生身份吗
Would that be Mr. Wren from Universal Heritage Insurance?
她五分钟后上班
You know, her shift starts in five minutes,
所以我们要四分钟内搞定
which means that ours starts in four.
他们在请一名行李员  一名礼宾员
They were hiring a bellhop and a concierge.
如何分工很明显了
The choice seemed obvious.
我昨晚面试了
I interviewed last night,
把你的简历弄得很突出
made sure that your resume would stand out.
对了  你在巴黎的筑鲁特西亚酒店
By the way, you worked at the Hotel Lutetia in Paris
工作了两年
for two years.
你可以凭员工卡进入任何一个房间
You'll have access to every room with your employee key card.
我可以在桌子前调查顾客
I can research the guests
侵入所有系统
and exploit any necessary systems from my desk.
酒店里有700多名顾客
700 guests in this hotel.
其中一位正策划谋杀
One of them is planning a murder.
我们从何入手呢
Where do we start?
哈罗德
Harold.
真高兴你能在短时间内马上就职
Glad you could start on such short notice.
德里克  这是我的荣幸
Derek, my pleasure.
工作时  叫我"福勒先生"
When you're on the clock, it's Mr. Fowler.
这位是巴德  门卫负责人
This is Bud, my head doorman.
你哪位来着
And you are again?
约翰  我曾在筑鲁特西亚酒店工作过
John. I worked at the Hotel Lutetia.
好吧
Right.
你的桌子在那边
Your desk is right over there.
记住  一定要优先推荐我们的餐厅
Remember, always recommend our restaurant
然后再说别家
before suggesting anywhere else.
-好的  -我们明天要举办
- Very good. - We're hosting an event
航空技术协会的活动
for the association of aviation technology tomorrow,
绝大部分参会者今天到达  所以
and most of the attendees are arriving today, so...
没理由闲站着
no excuse for standing around.
你还要等书面邀约不成
Are you waiting for a written invitation?
我来帮忙
Let me help you with that.
里瑟先生  米拉应该在清理房间
Mr. Reese, Mira should be housekeeping
在三十层
on the 30th floor.
我在12层送行李  马上过去
I just finished a run on 12. I'll head up.
约翰
John.
佐伊
Zoe.
离婚后就再没见了
Haven't seen you since the divorce.
你在工作
You working?
是啊  你在工作
Yeah. You working?
一直在
Always.
制服挺好
Like the suit.
在她推车上装摄像头了
I'm planting the camera on her cart.
我们可以随时查看她在哪里了
We can see exactly where she is at all times.
我没拿你的钱
I didn't take your money.
我钱包里有五十块  现在没了
I had 50 bucks in my wallet, and now I don't.
芬奇  谁在3024号房
Finch, who's in room 3024?
塔格・布兰特利  对抗力能量饮料的首席执行官
Tug Brantley, CEO of the Aggro Push Energy Drink.
我有这里的白金卡
I'm a platinum member of this place.
你知不知道
Do you have any idea
我能让你混得多惨
how difficult I can make your life?
-来吧  -你到底想怎么样
- Come on. - What do you want from me?
我想试试这双唇是否尝起来
I wanna know if those lips taste like
像你放在我枕边的巧克力薄荷一样
the chocolate mints you leave on my pillow.
你离开后我再来
I'm going to come back when you're not here.
你真的要拒绝我吗
Are you really going to turn me down?
-这里有问题吗  -谁要你进来的
- Is there a problem here? - Who invited you in?
里瑟先生  不要在午餐前就被炒掉行吗
Mr. Reese, could you try not to get fired before lunch?
有"白金卡"不代表你可以
Being a platinum member doesn't entitle you
性侵犯我们的员工
to sexually harass our staff.
如果您有异议  我们可以请警察来
If you disagree, we can have the police sort this out.
算你走运  我就不跟你老板告状了
You're lucky I don't report you to your boss.
-你还好吗  -没事
- Are you all right? - I'm fine.
这种事每周都会发生
That sort of thing happens every other week, you know.
我能应付
I could have handled it.
似乎这工作挺麻烦  我叫约翰
Sounds like a rough gig. I'm John.
米拉
Mira.
你这么又高又帅的人年纪轻轻来当行李员
So strong, handsome guy your age working as a bellhop,
肯定是走错过路了
must have made a wrong turn somewhere.
是啊  错得多了  我都懒得数了
Yeah, I stopped counting awhile back.
你自己现在的工作也够麻烦
Well you're in for a rough gig yourself.
我们那位天才经理
Our brilliant manager
本来应该雇四个行李员
should have staffed four bellhops.
但却只有你和兰迪
Instead, it's just you and Randy,
而他抽烟的时间比他搬行李的时间多
and he takes more smoke breaks than he does luggage.
你似乎对这里的情况很内行啊
You seem to know your way around this place.
酒店管理不容易  但也没多高深莫测
Hotel management is hard work, but it's not rocket science.
说到这个  我该回去干活儿了
Speaking of which, I should get back to work.
那就回见
Guess I'll be seeing you around then.
米拉
强制配对
完成
我真喜欢这姑娘  芬奇
I really like this girl, Finch.
我收到移民局的回复了
I heard back from immigration services.
米拉是塞尔维亚难民
Mira sought asylum as a Serbian refugee,
科索沃战争的幸存者
a survivor of the Kosovo War.
我还以为那场战争的难民都是阿尔巴尼亚人
I thought most refugees from that war were Albanian.
大部分是  但战争双方都遭受了损失
Most were, but both sides suffered losses.
鉴于米拉独自一人
Seeing as how Mira came alone,
我们只能认为  不论她之前的家庭如何
we can only assume that whatever family she had
现在都没有了
didn't make it out.
当时她16岁
She was 16 at the time.
从那时起她便一个人了
She's been on her own ever since.
这是中城区地图
Here's a map of midtown.
这里是剧场区  哥伦布圆环
That's the Theater District, Columbus Circle,
还有公园入口处
and the beginning of the park.
-从这里开始挺好  -多谢
- It's a good start. - Thank you.
我黑进了安保网络
I managed to hack into the security network
通过他们的信号
and piggyback on their feeds,
我能查看酒店所有的摄像头
allowing me access to all the hotel's cameras.
打扰一下  哪里有
Excuse me. Where's the--
女洗手间在那边
The ladies' is around--
男士的在另一边
and the gents', the opposite.
米拉
Mira.
有什么问题吗
Is something wrong?
警察问起了我们的  副业
Police were asking questions about our little side operation.
我在想  他们怎么会
It got me thinking about how they knew
想到来打探消息
to poke around in the first place.
-不是我  -当然不是
- It--it wasn't me. - No.
你不会傻到做出这种事
You're not stupid enough to do a thing like that
因为你知道  如果查出是你  我会有多愤怒
because you know how upset I would be if I found out it was you.
当然
Of course.
里瑟先生  我们得把酒店员工
Mr. Reese, we can add hotel staff
也加入潜在威胁名单中了
to our list of potential threats.
长官
Sir.
欢迎回到自由之地
Welcome back to the land of the free.
离开里克岛监狱花的时间比我预想得长
Getting out of Rikers took longer than I anticipated.
我知道  那位孤胆特工从你眼皮底下溜走了
I understand our rogue operative slipped away from you in there.
不会有下次了  我认得他的脸了
It won't happen again. I know his face now.
抓紧时间
Need you to work fast.
自从他攻击了我们的国防部设施
Ever since he assaulted our DOD facility,
我们的情报来源就被侵入了
our source has become compromised.
侵入了吗  长官
Compromised, sir?
此人牵扯到一个危险的组织
This man has connections to a dangerous party.
你必须找到他
It's imperative that you find him
并查出他为谁工作
and figure out who he works for.
他去的地方  通常都会有乱子
Wherever he goes, a mess usually follows.
我只要找到是哪个乱子就行
All I have to do is find the right mess.
我确定你能做到
I'm sure you'll work it out,
事成之后
and when you're done with him,
-确保没人能找到他  -明白
- make sure no one finds him. - Understood.
所有待命小组
Any available units,
请赶往46大街和3大街交口
please respond to a 10-50 in progress
有妨碍治安行为正在进行
at the intersection of 46th and 3rd.
-谢谢  -听我说
- Thanks. - Hey, so listen,
有件事情你得知道
there's something you should know.
我有一点  麻烦
I'm in a bit of... trouble.
-严重吗  -是的
- Serious. - Yeah.
我妈妈想撮合我
My mom wants to set me up
和她一位同教堂的女教友
with this woman who goes to her church.
-果然严重  -是的
- That's pretty serious. - Yeah.
你怎么说的
What'd you say?
说我在跟人交往了
That I'm seeing someone.
可能很认真[严肃]
It could be serious.
是吗
That right?
我不知道
I don't know.
你对你儿子提过吗
Have you told your son anything?
提过一两句
I may have mentioned a thing or two,
说我认识一个男人  人很好  很有趣
that I met a man who's nice and funny,
模样顺眼
easy on the eyes.
泰勒很为我高兴
Taylor's happy for me,
所以  你觉得见见他怎么样
so what do you think about meeting him?
我没问题  你呢
I'm cool with it. You?
我觉得是时候了
I think it might be time.
不过咱们回头再聊吧  我得走了
But let's talk more about it later. I gotta go.
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
联调局特工摩斯
SAIC Moss.
没想到我还会在这里看见你
Didn't think I'd ever see you here again.
我在忙唐纳利特工的事情
I'm on a matter regarding Special Agent Donnelly.
他死后  我就负责
After he died, I took it upon myself
复查他之前的文件
to review his old files.
发现了一些你可能感兴趣的东西
Found something that might interest you.
我发现了一封推荐你做探员的推荐信
I discovered a recommendation to make you a field agent.
唐纳利和你讨论过吗
Donnelly ever discuss that with you?
说过一两次
Once or twice, yeah.
我准备运作这件事了
I'm ready to run it up the flagpole,
前提是你还感兴趣
but only if you're still interested.
我感兴趣
I am.
很好
Great.
那么在你的许可之下
Then with your permission,
我们要开展背景调查了
we'll initiate the background check,
约见你的朋友  家人
interview friends, family,
过去十年间的任意联系人
any contacts from the past ten years.
好的  请随意
Okay, whatever you need.
今晚你方便进行测谎吗
Are you available to take a polygraph this evening?
-测谎  -标准程序
- Polygraph? - Standard procedure.
可以在你们分局进行
You can take it here in the precinct.
好的  没什么问题
Okay, it shouldn't be a problem.
-那就回见  -好的
- Then we'll see you later. - Okay.
联邦调查局啊
FBI, huh?
你真的要搞这个吗
You really gonna go through with this?
是啊
Yeah.
应该是吧
I guess so.
水疗位于电梯旁
The SPA's located past the elevator banks,
走过一道玻璃门  右手边
through a glass door on your right.
-就会看到的  -听起来不错
- You can't miss it. - Sounds great.
一切还好吗  里瑟先生
Everything all right, Mr. Reese?
感觉像回到了新兵训练营
I feel like I'm back at boot camp,
而我们仍对米拉的威胁一无所知
and we still haven't zeroed in on the threat to Mira yet.
之前见过这姑娘  陪的男人不一样了
Same girl we saw before, but she's with a different guy.
德里克经营的副业
The side operation Derek's running
可能是姑娘
might be girls.
我有同感
I made a similar observation.
卡特警探应该很快就会回复我
Detective Carter should be getting back to me soon
警方掌握的性交易活动
on any known solicitation activity.
瞧瞧谁闲到聊天呢
Look who has time to chat.
满载飞机专家的大巴刚到
A bus just arrived full of airplane geeks.
安排入住
Check them in,
别让他们在公共区域挤成团
and let's make sure they don't crowd up the common areas.
真心希望德里克就是威胁
I really hope Derek's the threat.
卡特警探
Detective Carter.
我问了风化组
I checked with Vice.
几天前他们根据匿名举报
They picked up a working girl a few days ago
在那酒店抓住了一个应召女郎
at that hotel off an anonymous tip,
但那姑娘什么都没说
but the girl didn't say boo,
不到一小时  保释金就到账了
and her bail was posted within an hour.
-谁付的  -巴德・加里森
- By whom? - By a guy named Bud Garrison.
楼层经理的跟班
Our floor manager's pet.
多谢
Thank you.
-还有别的吗  -还会有什么
- Anything else? - Should there be?
你应该  听到了我跟摩斯的对话了吧
I just assume you heard my conversation with Moss.
都听到了  警探
I hear everything, Detective.
那你也知道他想让我去联调局的事了
So you know he thinks I'm qualified to join the feds.
你怎么想
Well, what do you think?
如果这事能成  自然是个大好机会
I just think it'll be a great opportunity, assuming I get in.
你在担心测谎一事
You're concerned about the polygraph.
考虑到我为你们俩说了一年的谎
Considering I've been lying about you guys for over a year,
是有点
a little.
测谎仪其实测不出谎言
You know, polygraphs don't detect lies,
只是显示生理反应
just physiological responses.
试试在问到基线问题时撒谎
Try lying on one of the baseline questions,
这样或许能骗过测试仪
it might trick the test into thinking
把你的所有话都当正常
that everything you say is normal.
好吧  不过是机器而已  是吧
Yeah, it's just a machine, right?
能有多聪明呢
I mean, how smart can it be?
没错  机器而已
Exactly. Just a machine.
与此同时  为你着想
In the meantime, it might be wise for you
约翰和我就暂时先不联系你了
to steer clear of John and myself, just for the time being.
好  这主意不错
Yeah, I think that's a good idea.
谢了
Thanks.
看来德里克确实在经营卖淫服务
Looks like Derek is running an escort service.
如果是米拉告发了他  他可能就是威胁
If Mira called in the tip, he might be our threat.
快点确定  我们快点回家
The sooner we can confirm it, the sooner we can go home.
清理房间
Housekeeping.
不好意思  我们不用
Sorry, we don't need service.
我妻子忘记挂牌子了
My wife forgot to put the sign out.
没问题
No problem.
清理房间
Housekeeping.
我得跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
现在不行
I can't now.
你知道这事不能等
You know this can't wait.
里瑟先生
Mr. Reese?
米拉刚刚被3215房间的客人叫去了
Mira's just been summoned into room 3215 by a guest.
查尔斯・哈里斯
Charles Harris.
米拉好像不太高兴见到他
She didn't look particularly happy to see him.
你肯定累坏了  整天帮人提包
You must be exhausted, dropping bags off all day.
根据他的账单
According to his hotel bill,
哈里斯先生喝的比吃的多
Mr. Harris drinks more than he eats,
我们没法知道房间里的情况
and we have no way of knowing what's going on in the room
米拉把手机留在推车里了
because Mira left her phone on her cart.
你往上三个楼层就能找到她
She's three floors above you.
你的客房服务到几点
How late do you deliver room service?
酒店的客房服务到
I believe the hotel delivers room service--
我不要酒店的
I'm not talking about the hotel.
我要你的
I'm talking about you.
欢迎来我房间
Feel free to drop yourself off...
随时
anytime.
失陪
Excuse me.
我在32楼了
I'm on the 32nd floor now.
别逼我  哈里斯
Don't try to push me, Harris.
可你得听听理由
But you need to listen to reason.
你怎么会指望我答应这种事
How can you expect me to agree to this?
因为这是正义的事
Because it's the right thing to do.
说来容易
Easy for you to say.
下次记得敲门
Next time, damn well knock.
你来干嘛
What are you doing here?
我是来检查酒柜的
I was checking the minibar.
我来替你省省麻烦  酒柜空了
I'll save you the trouble. It's empty.
我们以后再谈
We'll talk later.
布洛兹女士  布洛兹女士
Ms. Brozi, Ms. Brozi!
请考虑一下
Please reconsider.
你是怎么回事
What's your problem?
这是你第二次跟踪我  闯进房间了
That's the second time you've walked in on me.
是德里克  对不对  他让你跟踪我
It's Derek, isn't it? He has you following me around.
你跟他之间有麻烦吗
Are you in some kind of trouble with him?
我知道他在酒店经营应召女郎生意
I know he's running girls out of here.
我还知道你牵涉其中
I also know you're involved.
我只清扫房间  这是我的工作
I clean the rooms, that's my job.
我工作很辛苦
I've worked too hard
没精力牵扯那些低级下流的事
to get involved in some sleazy scheme.
所以你就报警举报吗
Is that why you tipped off the police?
这不关你的事
That's none of your business.
刚那个酒鬼是怎么回事  我听到你嚷嚷了
What about the booze hound in there? I heard the yelling.
他不会伤害我的  没什么
He's harmless. It was nothing.
你确定吗  杜布瑞卡女士
Are you sure about that, Ms. Dobrica?
或者我该叫你布洛兹
Or is that "Brozi"?
你对我一无所知
You know nothing about me,
你不知道我的见闻  我的经历
what I've seen, what I've been through.
我不需要帮忙  特别是不需要你这样的人帮
I don't need help, especially from someone like you.
离我远点  懂了吗
Just stay away from me, got it?
酒店的牛排餐厅很不错  不过
We do have a good steakhouse here in the hotel, but...
我个人推荐格兰德餐厅
personally, I'd recommend the Grand.
全城最好的肋眼牛排  你们不会失望的
Best rib eye in town. You will not be disappointed.
我帮你们预定七点半的座吧
Shall I put you down for 7:30?
-当然  谢谢  -好的
- Sure, thanks. - Okay.
我调查了一下那位客人
I've been researching our guest.
查尔斯・哈里斯是名自由记者
Charles Harris is a freelance journalist
为好几家知名媒体工作
working with a number of respected publications.
他对各国领导人有非常强烈的个人观点
He's the kind of writer that has strong opinions about world leaders,
导致有半数国家都不欢迎他
making him persona non grata in a half dozen countries.
他为什么对米拉感兴趣
What's his interest in Mira?
不清楚  可他如此费心来找米拉
Not sure, but if he came all this way to talk to her,
米拉可能是他的消息来源
she might be some kind of source.
一位姑娘去国离乡改名换姓
A girl who flees her country and changes her name
肯定是不希望别人找到自己
is someone who doesn't want to be found.
可如果她是在躲藏  又是在躲谁呢
But if she's hiding, who's she hiding from?
那个穿着高领衫的男人
That guy in the turtleneck.
从我们来时他就一直坐那儿
He's been sitting there since we arrived.
你见他起身过吗
Have you seen him move at all?
-应该没有  -没错
- I don't believe so. - Yeah, well,
那个位置对前台和入口一览无遗
he's got a clear line of sight of the front desk and the entrance.
可能是在等人
Might be waiting for somebody.
如果不是呢
And if he's not?
那他还能是干什么呢
Then what's he still doing here?
你觉得我们要怎么查呢
How do you suggest we find out?
在看什么呢
What ya readin'?
没什么  我来时这书就在了
Nothing, it was here when I sat down.
好吧
Good.
真受不了那些飞机白痴
Can't stand these airplane nuts.
空中钩取是
I mean, the pickup--
天呐  真对不起
Oh, my gosh, I am so sorry.
-对不起  -没事的
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
没事  没事
It's okay, it's fine.
-对不起  -别放在心上
- I'm sorry. - Don't worry about it.
他在跟谁说话
Who's he talking to?
调出楼下的监控
Pull up the downstairs feeds.
看酒吧那个男人
Watch the man at the bar.
侧门的那个人接替了他的位置
The man at the side entrance is taking his place.
他们是监视者
They're spotters.
他们在轮换位置  以弥补监视缺口
They're rotating positions to patch the gaps in their surveillance.
军事侦察战略
Military recon tactic.
这是个杀手分队  芬奇
It's a hit squad, Finch.
至少现在能肯定我们找到了
At least it's safe to say that we found
针对米拉的真正威胁
the real threat to Mira.
可谁会派一队受过军事训练的杀手
Who would send a hit squad with military training
来杀一个酒店女佣呢
to kill a hotel maid?
监视者下楼去了  芬奇
Our spotter is headed back downstairs, Finch.
米拉在哪儿
Where's Mira?
她在厨房休息
She's in the kitchen, taking a break.
那我去检查一下他的房间
Well, I'm going to check out his room.
房客登记的名字是彼得・克雷格
That room is registered to a Peter Krieg,
用的是德国护照
Checked in under a German passport.
应该是假身份
Could be a forged identity.
我们得查出是谁派他们来的
We need to know who sent the team.
哈里斯那边有什么进展吗
Any new information on Harris?
我看见他的笔记本登陆了酒店无线网
I see that his laptop is signed onto the hotel Wi-Fi.
只要我绕过防火墙
If I can get past his firewall,
就能看到他对米拉的采访笔记
I can see what kind of notes he has on Mira.
监视者有一份哈里斯的档案
Our spotter has a file on Harris.
不管是因为什么
Whatever's going on,
一定与哈里斯写的系列报道有关
it has to do with a series of articles Harris wrote
都是针对塞尔维亚上校卢德克・彼得洛维奇的
about a Serbian Colonel named Rudko Petrovic.
彼得洛维奇速写: 战争罪犯
这名字真耳熟
That name sounds familiar.
卢德克・彼得洛维奇: 圣人还是罪人
我记得他正在竞选副总理
I believe he's running for deputy prime minister.
哈里斯的文章全都在指控他
Harris all but accused him
在科索沃犯下了战争罪
of committing war crimes in Kosovo.
米拉怎么卷入这事的
How does Mira fit into all this?
我好像查到了
I think I just found out.
我进入了哈里斯的电脑
I'm in Harris's computer.
阿尔巴尼亚出生证明
她真正的姓氏"布洛兹"
Not only is her real last name "Brozi",
她是阿尔巴尼亚人  不是塞尔维亚人
but she's ethnic Albanian, not Serbian.
根据哈里斯的采访笔记
According to Harris's notes,
米拉目击了彼得洛维奇
Mira witnessed Petrovic
下令处决她全家
order the execution of her entire family.
这就是为什么她向移民局
It makes sense that she lied to immigration
谎报名字和种族
about her name and ethnicity,
她只想保护自己
she was simply protecting herself.
哈里斯找到了一位
And Harris found the one witness
能够扳倒上校的目击证人
who could bring down the colonel.
他们一定是跟踪着他到了酒店
They must have followed him to the hotel,
期望他和线人取得联系
hoping he would establish contact with his source.
只要他们认出了米拉就会行动
They'll make their move on Mira as soon as they identify her.
他们可能已经开始行动了
They may already have.
我们的支援几时到
What's the ETA on our backup?
这就到了
Arriving as we speak.
又是酒吧
Always a bar.
给我杯姜汁汽水
Hi, give me a ginger ale.
里瑟先生  三名监视者
Mr. Reese, all three spotters
都回到了他们原先的位置
are back in their original positions.
看住他们  等会儿再处理
Keep an eye on them. We'll deal with those guys
我先把米拉送出去
after I get Mira out of here.
你就死不放手了  是吧
You just don't give up, do you?
约翰  侧门处那位行动了
John, the man at the side entrance is moving.
你就不能别管我吗
Why won't you just leave me alone?
这个理由充分吗
That a good enough reason?
他要杀我  因为我跟那记者谈过
He was going to kill me for talking to the journalist.
他要杀你  因为你知道
He was going to kill you for knowing
彼得洛维奇在科索沃对你家人的所作所为
what Petrovic did to your family in Kosovo.
那你是什么人呢
What does that make you?
只是个在正确时间到了正确地方的人
Just a guy at the right place at the right time.
皇冠酒店
32层走廊摄像头
被遮挡
搜索住客
哈里斯  查尔斯
获取主体手机
查尔斯・哈里斯
信号已找到  3215房间
侦测到枪击
型号: CZ99
种类: 半自动手枪
制造商: 扎斯塔瓦武器公司
产地: 塞尔维亚
失去连接
里瑟先生  我失去了哈里斯电脑的连接
Mr. Reese, I've lost the connection to Harris's computer...
还有他所在楼层的监控
and eyes on his floor.
你最好马上去哈里斯先生的房间
You'd better get to Mr. Harris's room immediately.
跟紧我
Stay close to me.
好了  我们从基本的问题开始吧
All right, like to start with a few basic questions.
你的名字是乔丝・卡特吗
Is your name Jocelyn Carter?
是的
Yes.
你是纽约警局凶案组的成员吗
Are you a member of the homicide task force in New York?
是的
Yes.
你曾抽过大麻吗
Have you ever smoked marijuana?
是的
Yes.
大学时
College.
你是第一个承认这种事的人
You're the first one to admit that.
好  现在开始问点重要的问题
Okay, now, we can move on to the important stuff.
里瑟先生
Mr. Reese?
似乎几分种前哈里斯先生
It seems that Mr. Harris remotely checked out of his room
远程退房结账了
a few minutes ago.
他不在这儿
He's not here.
有没有可能是其他女佣清理了房间
Any chance another maid cleaned this room?
今天不可能  这层楼是我负责的
Not today. This is my floor.
能看出有什么不对劲吗
You notice anything out of the ordinary?
这把椅子  一般是放在那里的
The chair-- it's usually over there.
我们来晚了
We're too late.
他们行动很快
They move fast.
尽可能清理过了
Cleaned up best they could.
我以为他是个酒鬼
I thought he was a drunk.
昨天  他说他知道我是谁
Yesterday, he tells me he knows who I am,
彼得洛维奇杀害了我全家
that Petrovic is the man who killed my family.
你是怎么逃脱的  米拉
How did you escape, Mira?
桑亚  住我家对面的塞尔维亚女人
Sanja, a Serbian woman across the street.
我在她家的阁楼上看到了一切
I watched it happen from her attic.
那个人  哈里斯  上个月找到了桑亚
Then the man, Harris, found Sanja last month,
录了像  她说我能够指认上校
Made a tape of her saying I could identify the colonel.
她两周前被发现死亡
She was found dead two weeks ago,
可能就是因为跟记者谈过
probably from talking to the journalist.
他说如果我公之于众  就能保证自身安全
He said if I went public, it would ensure my safety,
但我拒绝了
but I refused.
那个恶棍不择手段
Look how far this monster is willing to go.
我有其他选择吗
What choice do I have?
我要把你送出去  米拉
I'm gonna get you out of here, Mira,
但我得知道他们是怎么找到你的
but I need to know how they found out about you.
你把和哈里斯谈话的事情告诉其他人了吗
Did you tell anyone you were talking with Harris?
没  谁也没说
No, nobody.
那他们怎么得知你就是目击证人的
Then how could they have known you were the witness?
除非
Unless...
把你的手机给我
Give me your cell phone.
麦克风的电磁场
The electromagnetic field of a microphone...
会干扰
can interfere...
手机信号
with a cell phone.
他们监听了这个房间
They overheard everything in this room.
他们就在隔壁
They're next door.
在这儿等着
Wait here.
米拉
Mira?
她逃了  芬奇
She's running for it, Finch.
芬奇  她刚进了电梯
Finch, she just got on the elevator.
米拉  我正在找你呢
Mira, I was just looking for you.
里瑟先生  恐怕米拉正和
Mr. Reese, I'm afraid Mira's in there
另一名杀手分队成员在里面
with another member of the hit squad.
她无路可逃
And she has nowhere to run.
照我说的做
Do exactly as I say.
用你的卡让电梯直接到地下室
Use your key card and take us straight to the basement.
我也许能在电梯到达地下室之前停住
I may be able to stall the elevator before it gets to the basement,
让你有机会把米拉救出去
might give you a chance to get Mira out of there.
弗斯科
我现在有点忙  莱奈尔
I'm a little busy, Lionel.
那位职业杀手
Yeah, one of your trained killers
离开原位了
is leaving his post.
大堂的这位也一样
So is the one in the lobby.
他还带着一个大箱子
He's taking rather a large trunk with him.
我不知道他们要用来
I don't know what they could possibly--
天啊  是哈里斯
Oh, dear. It's Harris.
-他们要弃尸  -尸  什么尸
- They're disposing of the body. - Body? What body?
警探  你不能让他们离开酒店
Detective, you can't let them leave the hotel.
那段录像  在哪儿
The recording, where is it?
我不知道什么录像
I don't know of any recording.
桑亚的录像  你的老邻居
The one of Sanja, your old neighbor,
他房间里没有  电脑里也没有
It wasn't in his room or on his computer.
我发誓  我没有
I swear, I don't have it.
没有吗  太糟了
No? Too bad.
我不知道你是谁
I don't know who you are,
不过我不惜宰了你
but I'm prepared to shoot you
宰了二十个你这样的人  以拿到我要的东西
and 20 others like you to get what I came for.
真高兴你的枪法比你当行李员的水平高
Glad that you're a better shot than you are a bellhop.
同喜同喜
So am I.
警探  吧台那人
Detective, the barfly
刚通过后门离开了酒店
just left the building through the back exit.
明白  我正跟着呢
Yeah, okay, I'm on it.
-不好意思  -抱歉
- Excuse me. - Sorry.
我正在找洗手间  我觉得看到标志了  不过
Just looking for the bathroom. I thought I saw a sign, but--
你不如从那面的楼梯上到大堂去
Yeah, why don't you try right up those stairs in the lobby?
明白  谢了  兄弟
Yeah. Thanks, buddy.
带你离开这里怎么样
What do you say we get you out of here now?
还不行  我们得拿上哈里斯给桑亚录的像
Not yet. We have to get the tape Harris made of Sanja.
那是彼得洛维奇杀害她的证据
It's evidence Petrovic killed her.
你说你没有
You said you didn't have it.
我说谎了  他给了我光盘让我带回家看
I lied. He gave me a disc to take home and watch.
希望能说服我讲出自己的故事
Thought it would persuade me to tell my story.
在楼下我的更衣柜里
It's down in my locker.
那个加上你的证言
Well, that and your testimony
足以扳倒彼得洛维奇了
would be enough to put Petrovic away.
只要我能活到那天
Assuming I live long enough.
送你离开后我就去拿光盘
I'll come back for the disc after we get you out of here.
我们不知道还有多少杀手
We don't know how many hit men are left.
在下一层放我们下去  然后把电梯停掉
Drop us off on the next floor, then shut this elevator down.
你在跟谁说话
Who are you talking to?
你好
Hello.
我是哈罗德  和约翰一起的
This is Harold. I work with John.
很高兴认识你  米拉
It's a pleasure to meet you, Mira.
当然
Sure.
不好意思  伙计们
Hey, excuse me, guys.
你们看到一只吉娃娃了吗
Have you seen a little Chihuahua?
就是这么小的狗狗
He's a little dog about this big.
天啊
Jeez.
喂
Yeah.
有新任务给你
I've got a new assignment for you.
来大堂南配楼见我
Meet me at the annex south of the lobby.
好  没问题
Yeah, no problem.
顺便说一声  我没事
I'm fine, by the way,
反正我刚摆平两个
considering I just took out
企图弃尸的职业杀手
two trained killers trying to get rid of a body.
从未质疑过你的能力
Never doubted you for a second.
现在  过来见我
Now, come and meet me.
这就过去  我先上报这两个
I'll be right there. Let me just call these two in.
别忘了还有储藏室
And don't forget the guys in the storage room
和电梯里的
and the elevator.
不是吧
Seriously?
发现什么了
Got something?
皇冠酒店出乱子了
Big mess at the Coronet Hotel.
有几个人受了枪伤
Couple guys with gunshot wounds
被绑起来包成礼物了
have been tied up and gift-wrapped.
听上去像那个人
Sounds like our man.
那你还跟我说什么
What are you still talking to me for?
你那位朋友  是警察吗
This friend of yours, he's a policeman?
是的  米拉
Yeah. Listen, Mira,
他会带你去分局
he'll take you to his precinct.
这事结束前  那里是最安全的地方了
It's the safest place for you until this is over.
自从我离开科索沃就没感到真正的安全
I've never really felt safe since I left Kosovo.
我从那儿逃走时还是个小姑娘
I was a girl when I ran away.
新的名字  新的国家  我努力忘记过去
New name, new country, I tried to leave all that behind.
但感觉就像我一直在等着
But it's like I've just been waiting
过去的事再找上我
for all this to come back somehow,
担心着如果真的发生了我会怎么样
afraid of what would happen to me if it did.
在我看来
From what I've seen,
你比自己想象中更勇敢
you're a lot braver than you think.
我任由卢德克・彼得洛维奇逃脱了谋杀罪
I allowed Rudko Petrovic get away with murder.
我的家庭  桑亚  现在是哈里斯
My family, Sanja, now Harris.
不能再继续了
No more.
彼得洛维奇必须被绳之以法
Petrovic must be held accountable.
找我
You rang?
米拉  这是莱奈尔  你可以信任他
Mira, this is Lionel, and you can trust him.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
准备走了吗
All right, you ready?
谢谢你  约翰
Thank you, John.
不客气
You're welcome.
好了  来吧  这边
Okay, come on. This way.
芬奇
Finch,
你现在可以提出辞呈了
now would be a good time to tender your resignation.
清除应用程序
清除临时文件
清除历史记录
清除脚本处理
清除用户:临时系统管理员
你骗过你的同事吗
Have you ever lied to people you work with?
没有
No.
你是否在知情的情况下结交过通缉犯
Have you ever knowingly associated with a wanted criminal?
没有
No.
你是否
Have you--
怎么了
What was that about?
你如何描述你和
How would you describe your relationship
缉毒组警探卡尔・比彻的关系
with narcotics detective Cal Beecher?
卡尔
Cal?
你们是  纯友谊
You describe it as... platonic?
有性关系
Intimate?
我们是正式交往
We see each other socially.
你是否知道
Are you aware of any
内务部对比彻警探的一系列调查
of the several IAB investigations into Detective Beecher?
调查什么
Investigations for what?
我不便透露
I'm not at liberty to say.
这么说你不知道
So you were not aware of any
对他的任何调查
of the ongoing investigations--
不  我不知道
No. I was not aware.
酒店管理学
桑亚
你刚才死哪儿去了
Where the hell have you been?
你根本不知道酒店里正在发生什么
You really have no idea what's going on in your hotel,
是吧
do you?
你要是我  发现员工上班第一天
You're me. You find a first day employee
就偷偷溜进女更衣室
sneaking around in the ladies' locker room.
你会怎么办
What do you do?
不知道噢  这样吧
I don't know, something like this?
光盘到手了  回图书馆见
I've got the disc. Meet you back at the library.
找你真不容易
You're a hard man to find.
手机请给我
The phone please.
去个隐秘点的地方如何
How about we go somewhere a little more private?
问题真多啊
That's some line of questioning.
希望后面的容易些
Hope it gets easier from here.
很遗憾  不能继续了
Unfortunately, this can't go any further.
我要撤销你进调查局的工作邀请
I'm rescinding your offer to join the Bureau.
抱歉  警探  有时事情就是不如人意
I'm sorry, detective, sometimes these things don't work out.
为什么不行
Why not?
我不能透漏
I can't divulge that.
我在那间屋回答了一堆问题
I gave you plenty of answers in that room.
你至少该回报一个吧
I can get one from you.
以后
In the future,
选择伴侣时明智点
I'd choose my company more wisely.
-好  -好  行了
- Yeah. - Yeah, all right.
喝汽水吗
Can I get you a soda?
不用  谢谢
I'm fine. Thank you.
好  有需要就到外面找我  好吗
Okay, if you need anything, I'll be right out here, okay?
你错过好戏了
You missed all the fun.
神奇小子和我搞出了一场国际事件
Wonderboy and I jump-started an international incident.
真可惜我不在场
Shame I couldn't be there.
你说被抢劫了
You say you were mugged?
对  有人抢了我的钱包和手表
Yeah, guy took my wallet and my watch.
好的  稍等  先生
Okay. Just wait right here, sir.
一会儿会有人来录口供
Someone will be by shortly to take your statement.
谢了  哥们
Thanks, buddy.
出去
Get out.
Get out!
两种办法解决
This can go one of two ways.
应该没有一种是
Don't suppose one of those ways
让我活着走出去的
involves me walking out of here.
想来是没有
Didn't think so.
我不在乎你是谁
I don't care who you are.
我不在乎你是怎么来的
I don't care what you did to get here.
只想知道你为谁工作
All I want to know is who you work for.
我不会说的
But that would be telling.
话说你为何觉得我是在为别人工作
What makes you think I'm working for anyone, anyway?
因为你和我一样
Because you're like me.
不下命令  只管执行
We don't give orders, we execute them.
那是你吧
Speak for yourself.
最后问一次  你为谁工作
One last time. Who do you work for?
永远  别想  知道
You'll...never...know.
再深一点  我就会切断你的腹动脉了
Any deeper, and I would have cut your celiac artery.
二十分钟后  你就会失血死亡
You got about 20 minutes before you bleed to death.
你可以继续追我
You can keep coming after me,
或是去医院
or you can get to the hospital.
不知你的雇主
I wonder if your employers
会不会也对你这么慈悲
would have showed you that kind of mercy.
还顺利吧
How's it going?
还行  就是累了  漫长的一天
Fine, just tired, you know? Long day.
我在想我们和泰勒做什么好
I was thinking about what we could do with Taylor.
也许周六可以一起去植物园
Maybe we can go to the botanical garden Saturday.
是啊  我也一直在考虑这事
Yeah, I've been thinking about that.
也许进展太快了  你明白吗
Maybe it is too soon, you know?
好吧  没事
Sure. Cool.
卡特  如果你需要跟我谈谈
Hey, Carter, if you need to talk to me--
我只是需要点时间  仅此而已  卡尔
I just need time. That's it, Cal.
多久都没问题
You take as long as you need.
我不会离开
I'm not going anywhere.
-警官  有时间吗  -有
-Hey, Sarge. You have a second? - Yeah.
卡特  他有武器
Carter, he's got a weapon!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
看来你没错过好戏啊
Guess you didn't miss all the fun after all.
即时新闻
彼得洛维奇因战争罪受审 上校涉嫌杀害记者
上校的事业玩完了  下一站  海牙国际法庭
Colonel's career is over. Next stop, the Hague.
来杯和他一样的
I'll have what he's having.
话说你来这里是干什么啊
What was your business here anyway?
只能说那场会议不像
Well, let's just say the convention wasn't as boring
我想的那么无聊
as I thought it would be.
人们想摆脱在酒店里发生过的事
The things people try to get away with in hotels.
我知道是你们造成的这新闻
I see you boys made the news.
还不赖  特别是你们还帮忙
Not too bad, considering you also helped
拿下了个卖淫团伙
to take down an escort ring.
他们正好逮住楼层经理
They'd barely gotten the floor manager into handcuffs
供认他的全部罪行
before he confessed to the entire operation.
同时  我的手机响个不停
Meanwhile, my phone hasn't let up.
议员们要知道他们的名字
Councilmen needing to know that their names
不会出现在客户名单上
aren't gonna surface on the client list.
感谢你们的付出
I appreciate the work.
为了确保这里的适当运营
And to make sure this place is run properly,
哈罗德已经买下了酒店
Harold here bought the hotel.
这里需要适当的管理人员
It needed proper management.
约翰  哈罗德
John, Harold,
这轮酒店请
this one's on the house.
布洛兹女士  我想查看一下
Ms. Brozi, I was hoping we could go over
这个月的活动日历
the event calendar for the month.
没问题
Absolutely.
考虑过做办公室工作没
Ever consider doing in-house work?
这里需要有人做危机公关
This place could use someone in crisis management.
我喜欢到处走动
I like to move around.
自由工作  像你一样
More a freelancer, like you.
这地方不错
It's a nice place.
也许我会再待一个晚上
Maybe I'll even stick around for one more night.
听说房间全订出去了
Well, I heard it was all booked,
不过  你认识老板嘛
but then again, you do know the owner.
顶层套房
The penthouse suite.
再喝一轮
Another round?
先生  赫什先生来电
Sir, I have Mr. Hersh for you.
谢谢  梅女士
Thank you, Ms. May.
你有一阵子没消息了
Well, you haven't checked in for a while.
我遇到了阻碍
I hit a snag.
总部在面临更大的问题
We have a bigger problem at home.
我需要你尽快回来
I need you here ASAP.
我马上过来
I'm on my way.
梅女士  我要给国务院起草一封信函
Ms. May, I need to draft a letter to the State Department.
马上来  先生
Be right in, Sir.
为白宫晚宴准备的衣服
For your state dinner at the White House.
还有  我为您的结婚纪念日挑好了礼物
Also, I picked up something for your anniversary.
天  我忘得一干二净
God, I completely forgot.
梅女士  你才为我工作两个月
Ms. May, you've only worked for me for two months,
就已经比我还了解我自己了
and already, you know me better than I know myself.
这正是我来此的目的
That's what I'm here for.
可以开始了  先生
Ready when you are, Sir.
致国务卿  来自特别检察官办公室
To the Secretary of State, from Office of Special Counsel.